11 - Healthy: +5% more HP.
12 - Luck: +10% chance finding items
13 - Fame: more fame points awarded when choosing the correct choice
14 - Haggler: -10% deals at stores.
15 - Intelligence: Magicks have +5% damage.
		  Buffs last +5% longer.

1+2 = healthy
1+3 = luck
1+4 = fame
1+5 = haggler

2+3= intelligence
2+4 = Haggler
2+5 = healthy

3+4 = luck
3+5 = fame

4+5 intelligence


Level 1 =
Level 2 =
Level 3 =
Level 4 =
Level 5 =
Level 6 =
Level 7 =
Level 8 = 
Level 9 =
Level 10 =


BOOKS:

------------
RUOFL
Dying Earth

The ability to cause decay and deterioration amongst anything. With this, people who have Dying Earth can make things rot almost instantly if they desire, however, even if the user does not wish, his or her surroundings will slowly crumble, wherever they go. He or she is also cursed in that anything he or she creates will be instantly decayed, even some emotions. Thus they cannot create but only destroy.
CATALYSTS: Anything that is rotted or decayed makes a good catalyst for Dying Earth. Rotting flesh, decayed wood, even teeth. All contain the power of Dying Earth.
------------
CRESS
Bed of Thorns

The ability to manipulate and cause pain and sadness. People of the Bed of Thorns are psychic, being able to control minds at the cost of their own strength. However, they cannot damage people in this way, only cause tender emotions to burst. The Bed of Thorns concentrates on not hurting their opponent physically, but using mind tricks and words to wane their faith and make them feel useless. Cress's followers are known to look beautiful but quite creepy at the same time, being a devil under a beautiful body, bringing the saying "Every rose has its thorns".
CATALYSTS: Anything that causes small jolts of pain or is beautiful is a catalyst for Bed of Thorns. Needles, roses, and ornate knives work perfectly.
------------
TIRTH
Ragnarok

The ability to cause destruction and cause anyone they want to go mad with bloodlust. People of Ragnarok only want destruction, anarchy, and chaos in the world. Their unique personality forces anyone near them to turn into insane bloodlusting servants of Ragnarok. Ragnarok only wants a sea of chaos in the beautiful world, and cannot stand people who are happy. Ragnarok cannot stand Lysto, especially. There is no greater pleasure for Ragnarok than death.
CATALYSTS: Anything that is a product of hatred or causes destruction works. Baseball bats, fire, and glass are good.
------------
ARNIA
Ancient Moon

The ability to know everything and have the right solutions and theories for anything proposed. People of Ancient Moon are usually hard to understand due to their intensified intelligence. They are so advanced than others that they have a sixth sense - the ability to understand moods of others and define them. Glorified by their overwhelming brain power, Ancient Moon descendents are far too wise to be egotistic and place others who are not in their realm of intellect "still learning". In the presence of Ancient Moon, one cannot help but feel simply... stupid.
CATALYSTS: Anything that brings knowledge. Old books, newspapers, even televisions!
------------
LYSTO
Spring

The ability to diminish pain and agony with thoughts. People of Spring wish for peace, but they are not fully pacifists, as they will protect anyone they love from the forces of evil. They have the strange power to cure others of sadness and make them happy just by being near them, which makes them very popular. Spring will use any means necessary to protect loved ones and force back evil. They are chivalric and only want the world to flourish with happiness.
CATALYSTS: Anything that is peaceful, happy, or holy in nature. Blessed water, pretty flowers, and gentle breezes (can be caught in a jar).
------------



DESPERATUS SPELLS
------------------
Desperatus spells are spells that are incredibly more powerful than their regular counterparts. They are the same spells but they have much better damage or bonuses.

They are triggered by a "tension meter", similar to Allen's "damage meter". Except, the Tension Meter only fills up when HP is below 50%. Each hit contributes to tension building up, and when at max, the player can release Desperatus spells. Only certain high level spells can be Desperatus Spells. When releasing a Desperatus Spell, any damage or effect is multiplied by 200%, a cool bust-up plays, and the tension meter resets to 0.



MISERICORDE SPELLS
------------------
Misericorde spells are essentially the ultimate spell for each class. They cannot be used under the Desperatus meter, and the character will recite a poem for the spell/skill as it is being executed. The Misericorde spells for each class are as follows:

Saint Saviour - Vanquishing Sacral Spear
Bloody Angel - Raphael's Poem
Spikefist - A Sho Luo Bah Wang Chuen
Forsaken Knight - Memento Mori
Perfection - Thanatos's Poem
Blade Dancer - Dancing Blade
Destruct Clairvoyant - Chaos Spear
Blinded Archfiend - Starlight Symphony



RUNIC SPELLS
------------------
Ancient spells sealed away, only can be learned by collecting their scrolls and unlocking them with high-quality magic. They are powerful spells that require regeants to cast. They are written in Caelesian.



CORRUPTED MAGIC
------------------
Magic exclusively used and morphed by the Wretched. Forsaken Knight and Blinded Archfiend have to steal this types of magic because they no longer have innate magic. 



SONG WEAVING
------------------
As a tradeskill, you get the ability to compose songs to aid you in battle. Because you are Carriers, you have the ability to imbue music with awesome powers. When you compose a new song, it goes in your songbook for you to use. The songs grant different abilities, like giving a damage %, more health, or whatever.


=======================
  BASIC SKILLS: Allen
=======================


PALM SMASH-
Launcher; Smash something with your man-hand. A basic attack. Level 1 just does damage, but level 2 and above launch your target(s) into the air. Increased levels allow more targets to be hit.


RISOLUTO-
Passive. Permanently increases base Max HP by +2% each level for a max of +20% increase; not affected by buffs.
...PREREQUISITE: Palm Smash level 3


HEALING MELODY-
Healing DoT. Heals a certain amount of HP per level, with levels 4 and above being area-heals.
Formula = [Int+BaseLv/8*(4+SkillLvOfHeal*8) (/4 = per tick. it takes 8 seconds to fully recover, 2.0s tick time).
ex: Lv50, Int 30, using Lv7 heal = 50+30/8*(4+7*8)

Level 1 = 13 mp
Level 2 = 16 mp
Level 3 = 19 mp
Level 4 = 22 mp
Level 5 = 25 mp
Level 6 = 28 mp
Level 7 = 31 mp
Level 8 = 34 mp
Level 9 = 37 mp
Level 10 = 40 mp
...PREREQUISITE: Risoluto level 3


NATURAL♮NOTE-
Simply, cure status ailments. The max level is 3; the effects stack with each level so level 3 cures everything in 1 and 2.
Level 1 = Cure poison, burn
Level 2 = Cure silence, blind, bleeding
Level 3 = Cure paralysis, slow, charm, petrification
...PREREQUISITE: Healing Melody level 3


LEX DIVINA-
Traps a group of enemies in a divine cage. They can't be hurt, but they can't hurt you either. After being released, all enemies receive a debuff of -30% magic resistance.
...PREREQUISITE: Natural♮Note level 1


TWISTED KNUCKLE-
Midair; It is highly spammable and the faster you mash buttons, the more punches you throw. That's on the ground though, in midair you shoot 4385485 electric bolts at enemies.
...PREREQUISITE: Palm Smash level 2


FINAL DECISION-
Finisher; in midair, you'll instantly conjure a sword of light and swing it down, cutting dudes in half as you fall down. On the ground, after using twisted knuckle, you'll finish it off with a gigantic brofist punch.
...PREREQUISITE: Twisted Knuckle level 3


ELECTRIC CRASH-
This attack does minor damage but its main use is for paralyzing groups of enemies. Each level increases the amount of targets it can hit. Causes [Paralysis]
...PREREQUISITE: Divinity Crush level 3


ANGEL POACHING-
A very important prerequisite for Saint Saviour. Using this skill summons feathers. Each level (max is five) increases your total feather pool by +4. Every time you use this skill, it summons a quarter of your total feathers. (This is to make sure skills that cost more feathers are not used too easily.)
...PREREQUISITE: Heal level 3, Risoluto 5


FEATHER SHIELD-
Uses 2 feathers, and it creates a shield similar to Psychic Wall's responses. It either fails, breaks, or reflects. The %'s are exact to Psychic Wall's.

Level 1 = 3 hits = 10% Reflection = 30% Shatter = 60% Fail
Level 2 = 3 hits = 15% Reflection = 35% Shatter = 50% Fail
Level 3 = 4 hits = 20% Reflection = 35% Shatter = 45% Fail
Level 4 = 4 hits = 20% Reflection = 40% Shatter = 40% Fail
Level 5 = 5 hits = 25% Reflection = 40% Shatter = 35% Fail
Level 6 = 5 hits = 30% Reflection = 40% Shatter = 30% Fail
Level 7 = 6 hits = 30% Reflection = 45% Shatter = 25% Fail
Level 8 = 6 hits = 35% Reflection = 45% Shatter = 20% Fail
Level 9 = 7 hits = 35% Reflection = 50% Shatter = 15% Fail
Level 10= 8 hits = 40% Reflection = 50% Shatter = 10% Fail
...PREREQUISITE: Angel Poaching level 3


SHARP FEATHER-
{{-Desperatus Spell-}}
A damaging attack that uses one feather. It is long range and can cause [Bleeding] at a low chance. The damage is physical. (Razor feather is magical because it is a SS skill)
Level 1 = 100% dmg (str) 
Level 2 = 125% dmg (str) 
Level 3 = 150% dmg (str) 
Level 4 = 175% dmg (str) 
Level 5 = 200% dmg (str) 
...PREREQUISITE: Angel Poaching 1


PIERCING TOOTH-
Relauncher; Only usable if enemies are on the ground. You will smack them back up into the air and drive your fist through their backs. Higher skill levels means more enemies can be hit.
...PREREQUISITE: Piercing Tooth level 1


JUDGEMENTAL-
Jam your fist through an enemy's chest and rip out their heart. This is an awesome single-target only skill. Great for bosses!
...PREREQUISITE: Final Decision level 3


SYNTHETIC CHARGE-
Get a fake boost of strength via electrical charge. At level 3, it buffs all of your teammates.
...PREREQUISITE: Risoluto level 5


VOLTAGE SHIELD-
This is in bloody angel line, so either this or feather shield (in the SS line) can be learned. This provides an electric shield that lasts for a little while and when an enemy hits you, they get shocked and pushed back, also can cause [Paralysis].
...PREREQUISITE: Risoluto level 5, Piercing Tooth level 3


HOLY BOLT-
The second of the BA line. It's a spell thats based on not only your str but your int as well. It's a target-AOE that bolts anything near the enemy you chose. Enemies closer to the chosen receive more damage, and the radiation becomes less as enemies are farther away.
...PREREQUISITE: Voltage Shield level 1


FIST OF STORMS-
Your first actual AOE; it hits everything around you. No air-launching though, simply ground-based only.
...PREREQUISITE: Piercing Tooth level 3


MELIORATING SEAL-
*NOT LEARNED MANUALLY
A magic Seal that renews an area, healing all allies and damaging enemies with continuous divine magic.
Only usable if the area is blighted or damaged.


REVERSE DESECRATION-
*NOT LEARNED MANUALLY
A mass exorcism skill that calls upon holy power to aoe a small area of foes on the screen. With increased level, the power and area increases.


CORRUPTED MAGIC: BLADE OF LIGHT-
*NOT LEARNED MANUALLY
Summons Feres's power and turn your hand into a shining sword of light. You can't call on the dark sword because it will not respond to you. Instead, you can create a shield.


=======================
  BASIC SKILLS: FELIX
=======================


SHADOW SLASH-
Launcher; The basic attack skill. Disappear and then appear behind your target, as fast as the wind. Level 1 just does damage, but level 2 and above launch your target(s) into the air. Increased levels allow more targets to be hit.


ROMANTIC OSTINATO-
Midair; It is highly spammable and the faster you mash buttons, the more knives are thrown. Higher levels mean more targets can be hit.
...PREREQUISITE: Shadow Slash level 2


ARPEGGIO DE L'AMOUR-
Relauncher; you send a homing energy to a group of enemies on the ground and cause them to rise back up upon being hit.
...PREREQUISITE: Snake Eye level 1


COUP DE GRÂCE-
Finisher; when enemies are on the ground, you can slice their throats with a circular motion. Also, this can cause [Silence].
...PREREQUISITE: Romantic Ostinato level 2


SUICIDE RUSH-
Drains your own HP. But you do 20% more damage.

Level 1 = 10 Per 3 second
Level 2 = 8 Per 4 second
Level 3 = 6 Per 5 second
Level 4 = 5 Per 6 second
Level 5 = 4 Per 7 second
...PREREQUISITE: Bleeding Heart lvl 3


SFORZANDO SCREAM-
Felix throws his knives at an enemy's eyes, but as they are about to make contact, he teleports and slams them into the enemy's eyes. This is a single-target skill. Good for bosses.
...PREREQUISITE: Throatslitter lvl 3


BLOODBATH-
Your first real AOE. Slice up everything around you (point-blank) in swift slashes. Enemies stay on foot.
...PREREQUISITE: Snake Eye level 4


BITE-
Bite an enemy and drain blood. This in turn makes them take damage. The skill level is set at 1, and the % drained is always 5%. So 20 bites would restore your blood to full. It's a spammable skill, so as you use it, you latch onto an enemy and you have to spam to bite them enough times.
...PREREQUISITE: Shadow Slash lvl 2


GEMINI-
*NOT LEARNED MANUALLY
Revert from Felix to Chloe and vice versa.


DECAY MIRROR-
Slowly regenerate HP. When using this with Suicide Rush, Suicide Rush cancels out, and vice versa. The chart for Decay Mirror regeneration is backward from Suicide Rush.
...PREREQUISITE: Suicide Rush level 1, Throatslitter level 2, Teleport level 1


SCORDATURA-
Turn your violin into a killing machine (read: swinging it around like a fucking bat). While in this state, it becomes your primary weapon and you cannot use long range or skills. However, you receive a 30% boost in attack and 10% boost in attack speed. Additionally, each connecting hit takes a chunk off your Bloodbar (5%) because of the need to coat the violin with a psychic wall so it doesn't get destroyed.
...PREREQUISITE: Decay Mirror level 3


SHADOW SPHERE-
Summon a max of 5 shadow spheres that encircle you. If you get hit, they absorb x% damage and explode on the target, damaging them. Higher level means more spheres to summon. Each cast of this spell summons 1.

Level 1 = Max 1 Sphere, x = 3 (of damage taken)
Level 2 = Max 2 Sphere, x = 6 (of damage taken)
Level 3 = Max 3 Sphere, x = 9 (of damage taken)
Level 4 = Max 4 Sphere, x = 12 (of damage taken)
Level 5 = Max 5 Sphere, x = 15 (of damage taken)
...PREREQUISITE: Decay Mirror level 1


TELEPORT-
Invert space. Instantly move behind the targetted enemy & stun them. Can fail. At level 3, it's an aoe stun.

Level 1 = 30% Fail
Level 2 = 20% Fail
Level 3 = 10% Fail
...PREREQUISITE: Bite level 1


PSYCHIC WALL-
When cast, your wall has 3 reactions and a breaking point.
Reflection = The hit will reflect back to the target and inflict damage.
Shatter = The hit will break as it comes in contact with the wall.
Fail = The wall fails to protect you. It will still count as a hit if it fails.

Level 1 = 3 hits = 10% Reflection = 30% Shatter = 60% Fail
Level 2 = 3 hits = 15% Reflection = 35% Shatter = 50% Fail
Level 3 = 4 hits = 20% Reflection = 35% Shatter = 45% Fail
Level 4 = 4 hits = 20% Reflection = 40% Shatter = 40% Fail
Level 5 = 5 hits = 25% Reflection = 40% Shatter = 35% Fail
Level 6 = 5 hits = 30% Reflection = 40% Shatter = 30% Fail
Level 7 = 6 hits = 30% Reflection = 45% Shatter = 25% Fail
Level 8 = 6 hits = 35% Reflection = 45% Shatter = 20% Fail
Level 9 = 7 hits = 35% Reflection = 50% Shatter = 15% Fail
Level 10= 10 hits = 40% Reflection = 50% Shatter = 10% Fail
...PREREQUISITE: Psychic Lance level 3



PSYCHIC LANCE-
{{-Desperatus Spell-}}
Attack spell. Summon spears of pure mind flow to damage the enemy. This spell has a chance of stunning the enemy with each blow (5%).

Level 1 = 2 spears (75% int)
Level 2 = 3 spears (100% int dmg)
Level 3 = 4 spears (125% int dmg)
Level 4 = 5 spears (150% int dmg)
Level 5 = 6 spears (175% int dmg)
...PREREQUISITE: Psychic Bomb level 3



PSYCHIC BOMB-
The most basic psychic spell. Shoot a high-powered wave of energy.

Level 1 = 100% int dmg
Level 2 = 125% int dmg
Level 3 = 150% int dmg
Level 4 = 175% int dmg
Level 5 = 200% int dmg
Level 6 = 225% int dmg
Level 7 = 250% int dmg
Level 8 = 275% int dmg
Level 9 = 300% int dmg
Level 10 = 325% int dmg
...PREREQUISITE: Teleport level 1


PSYCHIC WRECK-
Can instantly kill 1 monster, so it's best to use it on very tough enemies. However, 1/3 of the current MP is taken away, and it has a high chance of failure.

Level 1 = 70% failure
Level 2 = 60% failure
Level 3 = 50% failure
Level 4 = 40% failure
Level 5 = 30% failure
...PREREQUISITE: Psychic Lance level 3, Psychic Wall level 3


PSYCHIC BOOMERANG-
This move kind of acts like chained lightning. It will home in on the target, and will subsequently hit whatever targets are around it in its path as it returns to you via circular motion, like a half-crescent. This can be spammed multiple times, but because of no cooldown, its damage is meager. It's possible to keep enemies in stunlock.

Level 1 = 30% int dmg
Level 2 = 40% int dmg
Level 3 = 50% int dmg
Level 4 = 60% int dmg
Level 5 = 70% int dmg
Level 6 = 80% int dmg
Level 7 = 90% int dmg
Level 8 = 100% int dmg
Level 9 = 110% int dmg
Level 10 = 120% int dmg
...PREREQUISITE: Teleport level 2


ATROPHIC SEAL-
*NOT LEARNED MANUALLY
A magic Seal that blights an area, forcing everything in it to decay over time (DOT).
Only usable if the area is in-tact.


CORRUPTED MAGIC: SHADOW CLAW-
*NOT LEARNED MANUALLY
Summons Kinos's power and turn your hands into swirling shadow claws.



=====================BLOODY ANGEL==========================
The judger of souls. The reliever of pain. His spells rip the sorrow and anguish from the human world and convert it to energy to tear his foes asunder. The Bloody Angel's spells mostly focus on a "damage meter," which absorbs pain. The pain stored within can be unleashed unto his enemies. He is decent at both physical and magical damage.


ABSORB SUFFERING-
*BLOODY ANGEL ONLY
The prerequisite to use Dispense Suffering and a bunch of other skills. Most skills depend on this skill being in use. When you use Absorb, you begin to take in energy of all damage recieved, thus filling up a "damage meter". The amount is based on the skill level.

Level 1 = 1/10
Level 2 = 1/5
Level 3 = 3/10
Level 4 = 2/5
Level 5 = 1/2
...PREREQUISITE: Holy Bolt level 3


TENSION EXPEL-
*BLOODY ANGEL ONLY
Release some of the anxiety you feel to restore some hp, and even cause [Refresh] status. The amount restored depends on the "damage meter". At level 3 it becomes an AOE [Refresh]; people standing next to you will feel your wave of tension be negated and feel better.
...PREREQUISITE: Absorb Suffering level 2


DISPENSE SUFFERING-
*BLOODY ANGEL ONLY
{{-Desperatus Spell-}}
An aoe that depends on the "damage meter". The skill is available for usage as long as Absorb is still on. The higher the "damage meter" is filled, the more the damage when Dispensing.
...PREREQUISITE: Absorb Suffering level 1


FAITHFUL-
*BLOODY ANGEL ONLY
Passive skill. Increases HP and defense.
...PREREQUISITE: Dispense Suffering level 2


HOLY WRATH-
*BLOODY ANGEL ONLY
Launcher; Blast a group of enemies with holy power to launch them into the air. This can cause [Blind]
...PREREQUISITE: Dispense Suffering level 1


MISPLACED FAITH-
*BLOODY ANGEL ONLY
Midair; you stay on the ground and shoot energy bolts at enemies in midair. the more you spam, the more bolts you throw. Can cause [Burn]
...PREREQUISITE: Holy Wrath level 3


ANCIENT BLOOD-
*BLOODY ANGEL ONLY
Finisher; Draw in the suffering and anguish of all the living and convert it to energy. Blast foes on the ground for this finisher. Can cause [Paralysis]
...PREREQUISITE: Misplaced Faith level 3


CELESTIAL LAUNCH-
*BLOODY ANGEL ONLY
Relauncher; pound enemies on the ground with a shockwave so that they are back in the air again.
...PREREQUISITE: Ancient Blood level 1


SANCTUARY SABER-
*BLOODY ANGEL ONLY
Restore x% of HP from the damage you have done with physical attacks. If the number restored is a decimal, floor it.

Level 1 = x: 5% of damage dealt
Level 2 = x: 10% of damage dealt
Level 3 = x: 15% of damage dealt
Level 4 = x: 20% of damage dealt
Level 5 = x: 25% of damage dealt
...PREREQUISITE: Faithful level 3


CINDERELLA WALK-
*BLOODY ANGEL ONLY
When this is cast, you will leave a trail of holy energy in your path. Anything that wanders onto this path takes damage and can obtain a random status ailment. The path gets wider and becomes a V the farther you walk, becoming a rather big area of infliction.
...PREREQUISITE: Sanctuary Saber level 2


CHERUB CADENZA-
*BLOODY ANGEL ONLY
Have a mystical melody be sung upon you by the cherubs in heaven. While this is active, little notes will hover around you, and a % of your magic power will increase as well as magic consumption decreased. At level 3, it's an AOE buff.
...PREREQUISITE: Cinderella Walk level 2


SERAPHIC NEEDLE-
*BLOODY ANGEL ONLY
The closer to death you are, the more damage this skill does. Magic power-based. This skill severely fucks up a linear path of enemies, and can cause [Confusion].
...PREREQUISITE: Sanctuary Saber level 3


HEAVEN'S FURY-
*BLOODY ANGEL ONLY
A one target attack. Does amazing damage, based on the "damage meter." Can cause [Slow]
...PREREQUISITE: Sanctuary Saber level 3


SOUL DIVIDE-
*BLOODY ANGEL ONLY
Exert a magic wave so powerful from pain that it can damage the enemy. This is a buff that halves damage to you and gives it back to the enemy. Higher levels increase the buff's duration.
...PREREQUISITE: Heaven's Fury level 3


RAPHAEL'S POEM-
*BLOODY ANGEL ONLY
The ultimate Bloody Angel technique that refers to the archangel Raphael.
...PREREQUISITE: Seraphic Needle level 2, Cherub Cadenza level 3, Ancient Blood level 3


======================DESTRUCT CLAIRVOYANT=================
The Destruct Clairvoyant has reached a point of mastery with psychic power. None can surpass the Clairvoyant's awesome power, having the ability to toy with anyone's mind and mold it into the way he pleases. He cannot physically damage well, but his magic power is incredible. The only thing the Destruct Clairvoyant fears is high Magic Defense... (note: as chloe, DC is the strongest "magic" type in the game)

BLAST CRUSADE-
*DESTRUCT CLAIRVOYANT ONLY
{{-Desperatus Spell-}}
An upgrade to Psychic bomb. Choose one enemy and create a blast radius around it, heavily damaging it and doing splash damage to those around it.

Level 1 = 400% int dmg (1 target); 150% splash
Level 2 = 425% int dmg (1 target); 125% splash
Level 3 = 450% int dmg (1 target); 175% splash
Level 4 = 475% int dmg (1 target); 200% splash
Level 5 = 500% int dmg (1 target); 225% splash
...PREREQUISITE: Psychic Bomb


EXERTED COAGULATION-
*DESTRUCT CLAIRVOYANT ONLY
Passive. Max level 5. Each level reduces the amount of blood used for spells by 10%; at max, it cuts blood requirements in half.


PSYCHIC MISSLE-
*DESTRUCT CLAIRVOYANT ONLY
{{-Desperatus Spell-}}
An upgrade to Psychic lance. Create a massive array of missiles and wound one foe for serious damage. Can cause [Stun].

Level 1 = 600% int dmg (Total)
Level 2 = 700% int dmg (Total)
Level 3 = 800% int dmg (Total)
...PREREQUISITE: Psychic Lance


BRAINMELT-
*DESTRUCT CLAIRVOYANT ONLY
Shock a group of enemies into a vegetative state, causing [Confusion] and doing DD.


FIGURE OF SPEECH-
*DESTRUCT CLAIRVOYANT ONLY
When an enemy casts a spell or uses a skill, this spell will punish them and hurt them. It has an initial aoe hit as well.


CEREBRAL COMBUST-
*DESTRUCT CLAIRVOYANT ONLY
An upgrade to Psychic Wreck. Fuck up the enemy's mind so bad that their brain explodes and they die. The chance is much higher but instead takes 1/5th mp.

Level 1 = 50% failure
Level 2 = 40% failure
Level 3 = 30% failure
Level 4 = 20% failure
Level 5 = 10% failure
...PREREQUISITE: Psychic Wreck


OCULIS CONTRACT-
*DESTRUCT CLAIRVOYANT ONLY
Pet skill emerges! Form a contract with an Oculis, a monster of shadow! He will assist you in battle, and increased levels of this gives him more HP and other base stats.


REVERSE CANTABILE-
*DESTRUCT CLAIRVOYANT ONLY
This is an DoT AoE that causes the opponents to hear screaming in their minds over and over again, and causes damage over time, with an initial damage starter.


SOOTHING CLARITY-
*DESTRUCT CLAIRVOYANT ONLY
Passive. Raises max INT by 2 each level. Max int possible is 20. If you have an Oculis, this will increase his INT and attack.
Max level 10.


PSYCHOKINESIS-
*DESTRUCT CLAIRVOYANT ONLY
A fun skill such as the Force in Star Wars where you can pick up surrounding objects and throw them at your enemies. Each level increases the heaviness of objects you can pick up.

Level 1 = Small objects
Level 2 = Medium objects
Level 3 = Large objects


LUCIDITY THEFT-
*DESTRUCT CLAIRVOYANT ONLY
Look into your target's mind... and tear out everything that they have hopes for. This causes you to trigger the "Clarity" condition in which you restore some mana every tick. It drains the enemy's mana and gives it to you.

Level 1 = 200% Int dmg
Level 2 = 250% Int dmg
Level 3 = 300% Int dmg
Level 4 = 350% Int dmg
Level 5 = 400% Int dmg


TELEPATHY-
*DESTRUCT CLAIRVOYANT ONLY
Like detect in pokemon, your party can evade most enemy attacks for 5 seconds after reading their mind.


CHAOS SPEAR-
*DESTRUCT CLAIRVOYANT ONLY
The ultimate Destruct Clairvoyant technique.


VAMPIRACY-
*DESTRUCT CLAIRVOYANT ONLY
An upgrade to Bite. This sucks a greater portion of blood from the enemy, in turn doing more damage, and it even sets the Refresh 
status on you for 10 seconds.


PARROT-
*DESTRUCT CLAIRVOYANT ONLY
Ah, the mimicry skill. This is what makes or breaks a good DC. When this skill is used, it mimics any skill that a monster just used, even A Sho Luo Bah Wang Chuen. However, the exceptions are the MAJOR boss skills, you know, the ones that tend to kill everyone on the screen. That is Parrot's only weakness. The catch? This has an extremely difficult skill tree to obtain.



======================PERFECTION=================
Relying on the God of Dying Earth's power, Perfection is just as the name is. A combination of magic and strength, he focuses on using dark power to shove his enemies off of the mortal coil. He loves death, he breathes death. He just cannot get enough of the sweet scent of rotting flesh. Perfection lives to violently extinguish the life of everything that exists. He is decent in both the magic and strength he wields.


RUOFL'S KISS-
*PERFECTION ONLY
Launcher AND Relauncher; A deadly poison homes on the targets and explodes in a venomous blast, causing [Poison] or [Charm] and launching enemies into the air.


SUFFOCATING ELEGY-
*PERFECTION ONLY
Midair; trap a large amount of enemies midair in a bubble of darkness as it slowly crushes them. The faster you spam the attack button, the faster the bubble crushes them and the more hits they take.


GLOOMHEART-
*PERFECTION ONLY
Finisher; With your evil hand, you rip out your opponents' hearts and do massive damage. Can induce [Bleeding]


SHADOW HOOK-
*PERFECTION ONLY
Summon a giant hand materialized from darkness to crush your foes. The accuracy and power of this hand increases with each level. Can cause [Paralysis][Burn]


JORMUNGANDR SHADE-
*PERFECTION ONLY
This is a point-blank aoe that causes a random status ailment to surrounding enemies. This NEVER fails, and can cause anything from instant death to poison.


MORTIFEROUS SABER-
*PERFECTION ONLY
Endows the party's weapons with darkness. It can cause random status ailments.


PETRIFYING CURSE-
*PERFECTION ONLY
Cast a horrid spell on your target, shattering their DEF by a substantial amount, [Poison]ing them, AND [Petrify]ing them as well. At higher levels, it becomes AOE.


VANITY-
*PERFECTION ONLY
Passive skill. Increases str and int with each level.


HARM TOUCH-
*PERFECTION ONLY
This skill is at first single target, but the effect radiates to other targets. It does some damage to the target, and then anything near the target gets hit with a wave of energy as well, causing a multitude of status effects: [Poison][Toxic][Paralysis][Burn][Bleeding]


UMBRAGE-
*PERFECTION ONLY
A darkness washes over the field. Dark element spells are enhanced by x%. All enemies on the screen are inflicted with [Blind], [Confusion] or [Sleep].


GLORIOUS DUSK-
*PERFECTION ONLY
AOE attk. It's point blank. Cloaking yourself, you emerge in the middle of your enemies, slicing them apart with your shadows. Has a chance of [Stun]ning enemies that have been hit.


THANATOS'S POEM-
*PERFECTION ONLY
The ultimate Perfection technique that references the god of death, Thanatos.

"With a heart of iron and a spirit devoid of pity,
Heaven refuses to accept a creature such as you.
The son of night and darkness, tearing lives in two,
Extinguishing human lives with tremendous alacrity."


WOUNDS OF THE SOUL-
*PERFECTION ONLY
A point-blank AOE debuff. By eating away at the targets' souls, their attack and magic defense is lowered and they become inflicted with [Silence]/[Frozen].


SHADOW PIN-
*PERFECTION ONLY
Pins the person's shadow in place so they cannot move. Similar to Astral Vine and Music Web; if it does not work, then it causes [Slow].


MACABRE SONATA-
{{-Desperatus Spell-}}
*PERFECTION ONLY
A pillar of shadow surrounds an enemy, and then closes in and traps them, suffocating them with darkness. This single-target attack is based upon your remaining MP.


======================BLADE DANCER=================
He is graceful as he is deadly. He is trained to handle his knives with ultimate dexterity and agility; he assassinates his enemies with elegance. The Blade Dancer's knife techniques have surpassed all, and cannot be matched by anyone else. His specialty is DoT attacks. As flowing and agile as his steps may be, he is a bit weak compared to Allen, with only his basic psychic spells to serve in the magic category. However, his speed makes up for this weakness, as he is still the strongest physical class compared to Perfection and Destruct Clairvoyant.


SHARP#NOTE-
*BLADE DANCER ONLY
Passive skill. Sharpens your blades, increasing passive ATK by +16% at lvl 10.


SYMPHONY OF SUFFERING-
*BLADE DANCER ONLY
Launcher; Strike a group of enemies before you with music and launch them into the air.


SAVAGE RONDO-
*BLADE DANCER ONLY
Following Symphony of Suffering. If midair, you will wildly spin vertically, hitting any enemies nearby. The faster you mash the attack button while this combo is in play, the faster you spin and more hits you do. On the ground, you do a crazy pirouette.


FOUNTAIN OF LOVE-
*BLADE DANCER ONLY
An AOE attack that releases a barrage of hearts and music from you, radiating out, and causing continual damage to those afflicted. With every tick, they have a chance of becoming [Charmed].


STACCATO-
*BLADE DANCER ONLY
Finisher; repeatedly stab a group of enemies on the ground. Can cause [Bleeding]


TOXIC RHAPSODY
*BLADE DANCER ONLY
Relauncher; release waves of poison from beneath the earth on enemies on the ground and relaunch them back into the air. Causes [Poison]


SKULL CLEAVE-
*BLADE DANCER ONLY
This does massive damage to a target depending on their CON stat, like Acid Demonstration. THe more CON, the more damage. This also causes [Bleeding] with a 100% chance. 


PRESTOSLICE-
*BLADE DANCER ONLY
Linear attack. Sprint across the field and destroy everything in your way. Flying enemies are immune to this. This is also a really good way to move about quickly, since you quickly dash in front. Causes [Slow]


PSYCHOTIC GRACE-
*BLADE DANCER ONLY
Buff. Increases dodge rate, attack speed and walking rate. This skill is very short due to the amazing increases. This uses blood.

Level 1 = 15 seconds, 20% Increase
Level 2 = 20 seconds, 25% Increase
Level 3 = 25 seconds, 30% Increase
Level 4 = 30 seconds, 35% Increase
Level 5 = 40 seconds, 50% Increase


POISON SABER-
*BLADE DANCER ONLY
Enchant your knives with poison, which of course gives them the chance to [Poison] some enemies upon contact. Higher levels mean more chance of inflicting [Poison] as well as [Toxic]


WRISTCUTTER
*BLADE DANCER ONLY
Passive skill. In exchange for decreasing your bloodbar, you passively increase defense. At max level, your bloodbar is crippled to 1/2, but your defense increases substantially.


VENOM AURA
*BLADE DANCER ONLY
A large toxic aura surrounds you. Get close to your enemies and they either get [Poison] or [Toxic]. Higher levels increase the chance of [Toxic] versus [Poison], and also increase the damage per tick.


BLOODY CURSE-
*BLADE DANCER ONLY
Curse all of your surrounding targets and drain their HP as well as restore your bloodbar. This skill costs a lot of MP to use due to the restoration of HP from all the targets. It is best to use it when surrounded.

Level 1 = 3% HP Restored, 3% damage
Level 2 = 6% HP Restored, 6% damage
Level 3 = 9% HP Restored, 9% damage
Level 4 = 12% HP Restored, 12% damage
Level 5 = 15% HP Restored, 15% damage



32-STAB SERENADE-
*BLADE DANCER ONLY
Rip an enemy into shreads with a fistful of knife stabs. The attack gets stronger by x% every time it hits. The base damage is dependent on your own dmg.

Level 1 = x: .25
Level 2 = x: .50
Level 3 = x: .75
Level 4 = x: 1.0
Level 5 = x: 1.25
Level 6 = x: 1.50
Level 7 = x: 1.75
Level 8 = x: 2.0
Level 9 = x: 2.25
Level 10 = x: 2.50


DANCING BLADE-
*BLADE DANCER ONLY
The ultimate Blade Dancer technique. Dance to the melody of your violin. Felix steps gracefully as he slices his enemies into thousands of pieces. While he dances, his other hands play the violin for him. This uses blood.

"A dagger that encrusts itself deep inside your core
is a blade that I wield carefully that makes you beg for more.
It dances swift, so gracefully, so deep inside your heart
A simple movement destroys the feeling that I rip apart."

======================SAINT SAVIOUR================
Saint Saviour focuses on magical holy power. He relies on his divine descent from the God of Spring. He is more inclined to healing spells, and is the ultimate vanquisher of evil. There is none more true nor blessed than he. Saint Saviour is a pro in magic, but his physical attacks are nothing to boast about.
	NOTE: While cursed, Angel Poaching is pointless to use because you can pluck your own feathers off of your wings. However, an additional skill must be used to regrow your wings. I mean, you ARE a son of a god of regrowth.

MUSICAL NOTATION-
*SAINT SAVIOUR ONLY
Increases Max MP by x%.

Formula = [.x * varMaxMP]

Level 1 = x: 2%
Level 2 = x: 4%
Level 3 = x: 6%
Level 4 = x: 8%
Level 5 = x: 10%
Level 6 = x: 12%
Level 7 = x: 14%
Level 8 = x: 16%
Level 9 = x: 18%
Level 10 = x: 20%
...PREREQUISITE: Angel Poaching level 5


REGROWTH-
*SAINT SAVIOUR ONLY
It regains 5% of your HP in 10 seconds, but the main point is that if your wings are damaged, they will be restored with this spell. Wings have an "ammo" of 200 feathers.
...PREREQUISITE: Natural♮Note level 3, Lex Divina level 1, Angel Poaching level 10


OPFERLIED-
*SAINT SAVIOUR ONLY
The only skill that's usable outside of curse form. Exactly like Shotgun, you have a 70% chance of instantly cursing yourself by fatally injuring yourself. If you're in the other 30%, you die. (The song is a song that Beethoven wrote, which translated, means, "Song of Sacrifice")
...PREREQUISITE: Opferlied level 1


RAZOR FEATHER-
*SAINT SAVIOUR ONLY
{{-Desperatus Spell-}}
This is an upgrade to Sharp feather. It is now based on int. Costs 2 feathers. Has a medium chance of causing [Bleeding]

Level 1 = 100% dmg int
Level 2 = 125% dmg  
Level 3 = 150% dmg
Level 4 = 175% dmg 
Level 5 = 200% dmg 
...PREREQUISITE: Sharp Feather level 5, Musical Notation level 1


BLOOD FEATHER-
*SAINT SAVIOUR ONLY
Uses 4 feathers to sink into skin of enemy and draw blood. Gain x% hp each. Has a high chance of causing [Bleeding] on the enemy

Level 1 = 200% dmg, x = 1
Level 2 = 225% dmg, x = 2
Level 3 = 250% dmg, x = 4
Level 4 = 275% dmg, x = 6	
Level 5 = 300% dmg, x = 8
...PREREQUISITE: Razor Feather level 3


DISTILLATION-
*SAINT SAVIOUR ONLY
A buff that renders you immune to all status effects and stat reducing spells.
...PREREQUISITE: Regrowth level 1, Heal level 5


HOLY BLESSING-
*SAINT SAVIOUR ONLY
Passive skill that increases DEF and MDEF. If you have a valkyrie, the valkyrie also gets the passive increases as well as bonus increases to her attack.
...PREREQUISITE: Blood Feather level 5


VALKYRJA CONTRACT-
*SAINT SAVIOUR ONLY
The pet class comes into play! You can summon a "pet" valkyrie to assist you in battle. Upgrades to this skill give her upgrades to her stats and give her more attacks. Teammate aoe buffs affect her as well.
...PREREQUISITE: Holy Blessing level 5


ANGEL FEATHER-
*SAINT SAVIOUR ONLY
Uses 4 feathers to restore x% of HP lost with each hit - so this is only 1 buff that requires 4 feathers to cast. This % chart is the same as Sanctuary Saber's. Sanctuary Saber however is for dealing damage -- like a Moon Saber -- Angel Feather is a damage healing spell.
...PREREQUISITE: Blood Feather level 3


FORGIVENESS FEATHER-
*SAINT SAVIOUR ONLY
Uses 10 feathers. A buff that revives upon death, like Guts from Valkyrie Profile. The chance is fixed.
...PREREQUISITE: Angel Feather level 3


ANGELIC AURA-
*SAINT SAVIOUR ONLY
{{-Desperatus Spell-}}
Absorbs a set amount of damage based on the level. It cannot be dispelled other than when it reaches its max amount of absorbed damage, or when it wears out. The duration is fixed, but the absorbed damage is increased with level. Uses 8 feathers.
...PREREQUISITE: Feather Shield level 5, Beatus Animus level 5, Angel Feather level 5


ASTRAL VINE-
*SAINT SAVIOUR ONLY
Your enemy becomes entrapped in a mystical vine and cannot move. At lvl 6 and above, it becomes AOE. After enemies escape from the vine, they have a chance of having [Slow].
...PREREQUISITE: Holy Blessing level 2


GRACEFUL FERMATA-
*SAINT SAVIOUR ONLY
A very powerful attack that uses 10 feathers. This is basically a huge shockwave across the screen, unavoidable. Think of Marisa's huge pillar of light she fires, except in 3d form.

Level 1 = 300% int
Level 2 = 350%
Level 3 = 400%
Level 4 = 450%
Level 5 = 500%
...PREREQUISITE: Forgiveness Feather level 4, Angelic Aura level 3


SERAPH BEAM-
*SAINT SAVIOUR ONLY
A holy spell that shoots a pillar of light from the sky to cleanse enemies. This spell is very powerful and has a high chance of causing [Blind] on enemies, with a slightly lower chance of causing [Burn].
...PREREQUISITE: Astral Vine level 3


VANQUISHING SACRAL SPEAR-
*SAINT SAVIOUR ONLY
The ultimate Saint Saviour technique. Summon one fuckin' gigantic holy spear to smash through the entire screen.

"From the surviving blessed fragment in my gaping heart,
I plead for the power of the sainted light.
The cleansing flame of hallowed strength
will repress the calamity that taints the Earth."
...PREREQUISITE: Graceful Fermata level 3, Grants level 3



======================SPIKEFIST====================
The Spikefist focuses on pummeling his opponents with his devistating punches. He knows all weaknesses of the human body, and does not hesitate to take advantage of his enemies. He has trained himself to utilize his strength and conserve it for when it is truly needed. His martial arts skills are unmatched to all, but he is lacking in the magical category. 


FORCE PALM-
*SPIKEFIST ONLY
Launcher; An upgrade to Palm Smash.
...PREREQUISITE: Palm Smash 5


KNUCKLECRASHER-
Passive. Increases damage and accuracy.

Level 1 = +2% Accuracy, +5 ATK
Level 2 = +4% Accuracy, +15 ATK
Level 3 = +6% Accuracy, +30 ATK
Level 4 = +8% Accuracy, +40 ATK
Level 5 = +10% Accuracy, +50 ATK
...PREREQUISITE: None


BLITZKRIEG-
*SPIKEFIST ONLY
Midair; A "semi-upgrade" to Twisted Knuckle since you only can use it once before enemies fall. Perfect for using right after Furious Knuckle. You deliver some crazy-ass lightning punches to enemies midair. Keep in mind that you must be on the ground to cast this, you will automatically go mid-air and target anything in your range when you cast. The level increases the number of hits the skill does. (NOTE: It's exactly like Warrior from Dragonica's spinny attack)
...PREREQUISITE: Force Palm level 2


FURIOUS KNUCKLE-
*SPIKEFIST ONLY
A "sort of" upgrade to Fist of Storms. It's also an AOE, but it launches enemies into the air.
...PREREQUISITE: Blitzkrieg level 1


VOLTAIC CONVULSION-
*SPIKEFIST ONLY
Finisher; it takes some of your HP though. Only usable when enemies are on the ground, you go nutso and release a ton of electrically charged energy in a vicinity, which damages anything on the ground. Has a high chance of causing [Paralysis]
...PREREQUISITE: Blitzkrieg level 3


HEADCRUSHER-
*SPIKEFIST ONLY
Relauncher; Stomp on enemies' heads, and throw them back upwards.
...PREREQUISITE: Voltaic Convulsion level 1


BRAINSPASM-
*SPIKEFIST ONLY
You go totally insane, in fact so insane that you can't even control your own character. for 10 mana/s, you dish out twice your damage and go twice as fast, but take twice the damage than normal.
...PREREQUISITE: Voltaic Convulsion level 3


LIGHTNING SABER-
*SPIKEFIST ONLY
Form a magic energy to power up your strikes and have a chance of causing [Paralysis] or, a lower chance, [Stun]. Every level increases the chance of inflicting it.
...PREREQUISITE: Knucklecrasher level 2


ELECTRIC SWEEP-
*SPIKEFIST ONLY
Knock your enemy to the ground with a dazzling kick, causing [Stun].
...PREREQUISITE: Lightning Saber level 2


BLEEDING FIST-
*SPIKEFIST ONLY
Used mostly on boss fights. Sucks 15% life from the opponent for 10 seconds. This can only be used once per monster. (booleans on the monsters)

Level 1 = 10% success
Level 2 = 30% success
Level 3 = 50% success
Level 4 = 70% success
Level 5 = 90% success
...PREREQUISITE: Lightning Saber level 2


IMPACT ASSAULT-
*SPIKEFIST ONLY
Summon energy to your hands and do a kame-hame-ha, a linear attack.
...PREREQUISITE: Electric Sweetp level 2


THOUSAND FIST STRIKE-
*SPIKEFIST ONLY
An upgrade of Judgemental; it's a nice single-target skill that does quite a bit of damage. It can cause [Paralysis]
...PREREQUISITE: Impact Assault level 3


PRESSURE POINT-
*SPIKEFIST ONLY
Strike a pressure point to cause [Bleeding] to enemies. It has a very high critical chance. Higher levels means more targets.
...PREREQUISITE: Bleeding Fist level 2


FOCUS ENERGY-
*SPIKEFIST ONLY
A buff that increases your critical rate by x% each level. At level 3 it becomes AOE.
...PREREQUISITE: Pressure Point level 3


INDRA'S ARROW-
*SPIKEFIST ONLY
The ultimate Spikefist technique, which references the Hindu god of rain, lightning, and thunder, Indra. This spell sucks all of your MP and unleashes a deadly blow. Because of the incredible surge of energy that passed through your body, you are unable to recover MP for three minutes, even potions don't work.

Formula = [(Skill level * Weapon power * Strength) + (Added Power + Level * Remaining MP)] / Monster Level

Level 1 = 500 Power
Level 2 = 1000 Power
Level 3 = 1500 Power
Level 4 = 2000 Power
Level 5 = 3000 Power

CALCULATION: Allen 45 STR / 40 Weapon Power / Skill 5 / 3000 power / level 23 / 300 MP / Monster lvl 35
...PREREQUISITE: Brainspasm level 4, Thousand Fist Strike level 3



======================FORSAKEN KNIGHT====================
He has given up his angelic stature to turn to the darkness. The Forsaken Knight has the strength of an ogre and wields the power of ten thousand slain souls. His holy magic depleted, he can only rely on corrupted magic for his dark spells. He is a little slow in combat, but this weakness is easily overcome by his sheer power.


CORRUPTED MAGIC: DEATH OF A GOD-
*FORSAKEN KNIGHT ONLY
Learned from any Wretched. A basic attack skill. You jump up above your enemy and plunge your sword straight into their skull.


CORRUPTED MAGIC: EMOTIONLESS-
*FORSAKEN KNIGHT ONLY
Learned from Feres. This passive skill increases DEF.


CORRUPTED MAGIC: ONE THOUSAND SPLINTERED SUNS-
*FORSAKEN KNIGHT ONLY
Learned from Argus. With your sword, you slice the sun into a thousand pieces, and the pieces rain down on your enemies, as well as causing Burning/Blind status effect(s). A fun thing about this skill is that if it's daytime, it will instantly set the timer to night!


CORRUPTED MAGIC: ABSORB SPELL-
*FORSAKEN KNIGHT ONLY
Learned from Seras. This absorbs spells and adds them to your mana pool.


CORRUPTED MAGIC: GRAPPLING SHADOW-
*FORSAKEN KNIGHT ONLY
Learned from Kinos. This engulfs a target with shadow, causing a DOT and slowing down their movement.


CORRUPTED MAGIC: CHAOTIC EARTH-
*FORSAKEN KNIGHT ONLY
Learned from Kinos or Feres. This AOE splits the ground in half with your sword, causing an earthquake and damaging enemies.


CORRUPTED MAGIC: DICTATORSHIP-
*FORSAKEN KNIGHT ONLY
Learned from Feres or Argus. This is an attack that rends the target, slicing them in two, and steals their HP and gives it back to you.


CORRUPTED MAGIC: UNNERVING GLARE-
*FORSAKEN KNIGHT ONLY
Learned from Seras. This skill does no damage, but decreases enemy defense and dodge.


CORRUPTED MAGIC: SHADOW SABER-
*FORSAKEN KNIGHT ONLY
Learned from Kinos. Imbues the weapon with shadow and the power to [Petrify].


CORRUPTED MAGIC: MEMENTO MORI-
*FORSAKEN KNIGHT ONLY
Learned from Argus. "Remember, you must die." You slice off the head of every single enemy on the screen, having their heads immediately turn and rot to skulls.

======================BLINDED ARCHFIEND====================
Relinquishing his dark past, the Archfiend opens himself to a more divine, angelic status -- wielding a bow of light and a magical saber, he can only use the corrupted magic learned from the Wretched. His psychic power is taken away, and his hands dead, but he makes up with the lack of former powers with incredible strength.


CORRUPTED MAGIC: REFLECT SPELL-
*BLINDED ARCHFIEND ONLY
Learned from Seras. This reflects spells back at the caster, causing the [Mirror] status 


CORRUPTED MAGIC: CRESCENT LIGHT-
*BLINDED ARCHFIEND ONLY
Learned from any Wretched. A basic attack skill. This emits a shockwave of light from your bow that slices through your opponent.


CORRUPTED MAGIC: SHINE SABER-
*BLINDED ARCHFIEND ONLY
Learned from Feres. When cast, your weapon has the ability to [Blind] and do extra damage to enemies.


CORRUPTED MAGIC: GODLY FAVOUR-
*BLINDED ARCHFIEND ONLY
Learned from Valis. Protects you with a magic shell that lessens damage from your enemies.


CORRUPTED MAGIC: DIVINE RAY-
*BLINDED ARCHFIEND ONLY
Learned from Feres. Shoot up a bunch of light arrows, and they rain down on your enemies in an AOE attack, much like an arrow shower.


CORRUPTED MAGIC: STAR LANCE-
*BLINDED ARCHFIEND ONLY
Learned from Seras. Charge up your bow, creating a huge arrow, and shoot it at an enemy. It will explode, and cause splash.


CORRUPTED MAGIC: LINGERING THOUGHT-
*BLINDED ARCHFIEND ONLY
Learned from Kinos. This passive skill increases AGI.


CORRUPTED MAGIC: BEAUTY THEFT-
*BLINDED ARCHFIEND ONLY
Learned from Valis. This skill can suck HP from a target.


CORRUPTED MAGIC: STARLIGHT SYMPHONY-
*BLINDED ARCHFIEND ONLY
Learned from Kinos. Play a melody to gain the favour of the stars, and subsequently have them rain upon your foes. Its range is much wider than Divine Ray, and it basically hits EVERYTHING on the screen.


============================================================================
				undefined

	FELIX:
NECROTIC PRINCE'S CHARIOT-
Summons a skeletal chariot for Felix to ride in across the screen, pummeling
everything in the way for MASSIVE DAMAGE.



============================================================================


Paths for FELIX:

PERFECTION -> Ruofl's Curse
BLADE DANCER -> Knives
DESTRUCT CLAIRVOYANT -> Psychic
BLINDED ARCHFIEND -> Holy magic. Must steal corrupted magic from Wretched.



Paths for Allen:

BLOODY ANGEL -> Lysto's Curse
SPIKEFIST -> Knuckles
SAINT SAVIOUR -> Holy magic
FORSAKEN KNIGHT -> Shadow magic. Must steal Corrupted Magic from Wretched.