Westminster.
-Name of a popular bar?
-small hospital?
-another semi popular church?
-a big popular hospital?
NRO Tenchu: club = strawberry moons
NRO Tenchu: hospital = great ormand street or st marys
NRO Tenchu: church = westminster abbey or cathedral

The Westminster abbey is "the traditional place of coronation and burial site for English monarchs." 

IMPORTANT EVENTS IN 1965:
January 24 - Winston Churchill dies at the age of 90, as the result of a stroke he suffered on January 15.
March 18 - Rolling Stones Mick Jagger, Keith Richards, and Bill Wyman are fined five pounds for urinating on the wall of a London gas station. The band had asked to use the restroom, but it was out of order.
August 1 - Cigarette advertising is banned on British television
August 6 - The beatles release "Help!" album.
August 15 - The Beatles play Shea Stadium, which was the first rock concert to be held in a venue of that size. The concert also set new world records for attendance (55,600+) and for revenue. (this was in new york.)
The crime rate in britain was increasing because the police were too busy solving crimes rather than preventing.
All four countries witnessed steep rises in crime and anti-social behaviour following the cultural revolution of the 1960s, which broke down shared norms of acceptable behaviour.
In 1955 fewer than 500,000 crimes were recorded by the police in England and Wales. By the end of the 1960s there were over 1.5 million. By the end of the 1970s there were 2.7 million (p.xii). In 1964 in England and Wales there were 72,000 domestic burglaries; in 2003/04 there were 402,000. The main point is, England's crime rate skyrockets in the 1960's.
Suicides in England and Wales 1966: 4,994


TV - The show "Coronation Street." It is a soap opera, very high-rated in the UK. nicknames are 'Corrie' or 'the street.' Television started to become popular in the 60s but not everyone could afford a set. Coloured TV got popular in 1961. 
"The Avengers" show. A spy-fi genre, with secret agent and science fiction.

EDUCATION: In those days classes would be lucky to have a radio, TV or a tape recorder. Also in the 1960s and 70s free milk was given to children at break time. In the 1960s they did English, maths, reading, spellings, tables, art and P.E. as we do. Instead of science, history and geography these subjects were bundled together under the umbrella of nature study in some schools. Craft work was an afternoon subject where the boys went to one teacher and did handiwork while the girls went to another teacher to do needlework and knitting.

ENTERTAINMENT - In the 60s the cinema and theatre would have been the main source of entertainment besides the TV. Free time was spent mainly playing outside and when inside board games were popular. 

MUSIC - The Beatles, The Dave Clark Five, The Rolling Stones, The Tremeloes, The Animals, The Kinks

CITY - In the sixties there were a lot of locally owned shops like the butcher, grocer and greengrocer and people shopped three or four times a week. 

COMMUNICATION - In the 1960s letter writing was the main form of communication although some people had a telephone. 

MONEY: £1 = a pound. 20 shillings is £1. one shilling is a "bob."
12 pennies in 1 shilling
240 pennies in 1 £1
a crown is £5.
Ten shillings is called a half-sovereign.
A £1 coin is called a Sovereign. It was made of gold.
The average wage for clerical work was £11.
 
RELIGION - mostly everyone is christian. for hells sake ill make the cast all catholic and theyll go to church on sundays.

GANGS - Gangsters couldnt afford handguns so they relied on fists, bicycle chains, rocks, switchblades, baseball bats. In the 1950's gangs didn't fight over drugs. Drive by shootings were rare, and the gangs were mostly comprised of teenagers aged 12-19. Although drugs were prevalent in New York City, particularly with the rise of heroin in the late 50's and into the 60's, the gang wars were mostly fought over "turf" and girls. 

CANNIBALS - Sascha Spesiwtsew,